foreign
well it's not important so you said the
wrong thing again
yeah for us to do it
people don't realize you gotta wait for
them
here is
just waiting for him
okay
you're not fighting at all I'm not
fighting anymore I'm not pushing
I'm not pushing now we just walk
straight through
okay I'll walk straight through nothing
there sitting there without any effort
change that
he goes
well it's because
the um
I moved at a fraction well I put that I
took all I feel there
okay I want to see if I can do it on the
back side yeah
shouldn't be magnetizing the boys don't
need them if it is
magnetite yeah
you're trying to push him in to the
fields you try and push them you'll feel
the feels and they'll be fighting each
other and everything else as you're
coming in closer like that you can feel
the feel this it just dissipates so you
gotta wait for it yeah wait for it you
see with the round ones all I do is I
just sit there hold them out into this
field where it just starts okay where it
just that's pulsing there you can see it
just push pushes me down so I just wait
I thought I had to bring something
that's just magic no magic yeah well you
know
this one's a bit harder I'm not pushing
I'm not fighting this I'm not fighting
him
he's losing his power because these are
hardly yeah they're they're deadly hear
about those magnets are deadly this
thing here is nearly flat then iodium
sorry
okay I'll just wait for a bigger number
two minutes yep okay she's letting go
she's got no Field Effect at all but
they're not magnetic anymore
I better charge him again
real strong again I can wind him right
up because I'm winding right down
that's a bit more
themselves
what why not how do you think you're
making magnet see this is the funny
thing you're you're making
that's stronger right
yeah I think when you pull them off at
first
that will fade out back to where they
normally charged you okay I'll just
waiting them up a bit just what you're
doing is you don't walk try and fight
them you walk in the same as you walk
them out and make them discharge right
you film I just started to walk them
into that Enfield right I couldn't get
it around I just felt them pick up and
then whack they slide past each other
and think she's improving
um
and to create a magnet you can either
drag a piece of wine across you know
another magnet but don't make them weak
you can pull it across batteries okay or
you can grab um a copper wire and you
can wrap it around you get a battery
right doesn't that with AC you get it
with a DC and you wrap it around a
certain way so if you've got a piece of
iron and you wrapped it around clockwise
and and plug both onto the battery it
does it's not a dead short okay as long
as you've got a certain amount of
windings yeah 17. so
you put it on and so on like that and
that will send a magnetic field in your
piece of iron but what it'll do is it'll
put North one in and set out the other
and usually if you wind it clockwise
you'll put the um you'll put the fields
there it doesn't have to be this way so
don't don't go by me you don't
understand one way is you'll put a field
the she'll put a South Pole towards the
negative end of the terminal you've
winded the opposite way
and she will put North Pole against
North Pole negative South Pole again
South Pole positive fuel reverse the
pole on your Magnum one just by
whichever way that you turn your coil
around the piece
so these are these are things that
within what you're doing here now
your magnetic fields are still within
that magnet even though I took them away
but by taking them away if I can take
him away I can put poles together
right what shouldn't be together you
know you're fighting poles they'll
actually come together when I take the
field out of the magnets I can turn the
magnet right around
so what should not come together
actually just goes straight together and
then if you charge them again those damn
things they won't repel
they stay together and they should throw
themselves to Pieces but what they're
doing is they're putting out and an
opposite field on each
on Egypt right or shouldn't be there
okay so they've put two of the same
fuels together in the center or
shouldn't come together and they put two
of the same Fields both directions on
each end
and you're not a man of electricity
output that you get off that uh look at
the lightning electricity because you
haven't got opposite fields to it thank
you you get double I feel no because you
don't destroy the dark polarity yeah go
ahead so to show you the differences
what we're talking about with magnet
magnet Fields what you can't do is you
can't have this tape on when I can go
and show you what I've got up here right
yeah not a problem it's just this is
other people's experimental stuff yeah
all right it's mine but I've done stuff
for them yeah good yeah and I'll pull
things apart and so on like that and um
and so on so to show you this I can't
have you go it's not mine to say so
because it's not my stuff is not
available to the public yeah fair enough
they're saying that it's not even
available to you the private people yeah
it's just it's not a valuable period
Well
well fair enough I just don't do to make
a profit I don't do for praise and glory
I don't do for I don't do
I have no reason to do what I do I just
find these things I do them and that's
what happens so it's other people who
try and take my name and put it out
there and tell the people who try and
make out on the famous guy I'm not
famous I'm not nothing I don't want to
be famous I don't want to be known for
anything just a simple Ordinary Boy
don't care
something I care it's just
I don't care about all those things that
other people care about
um
I don't care what it means to do any of
this stuff
like I can run cars if it meant that I
run cars without
um you know petrol and everything else
but I don't